Now in this first real lesson we're gonna start with description description means being able to explain
现在在第一个真正的课程中，我们将从描述开始，描述意味着能够解释
what something actually looks like.
什么东西实际上看起来像。
Or to give details about something so that other people can really understand.
或提供有关某事的详细信息，以便其他人能够真正理解。
We're going to talk about description first because it's so important whether you're telling somebody
我们将首先讨论描述，因为无论您是否告诉某人，这一点都非常重要
what to do how to do something what something looks like.
做什么 怎么做 某事看起来像什么。
For example if you're on the phone and you're talking to somebody you need to be able to explain sometimes
例如，如果您正在打电话并且正在与某人交谈，您有时需要能够解释
where to go or what you're looking at because you're on the phone.
去哪里或正在看什么，因为你在打电话。
They can't see what you're seeing.
他们看不到你所看到的。
So if you're able to describe something very very clearly then you'll be very very powerful.
所以如果你能够非常非常清楚地描述一些事情，那么你就会非常非常强大。
OK.
好的。
So in this first real lesson we're going to focus on that because it's the foundation of a lot of basic
所以在第一个真正的课程中，我们将专注于这一点，因为它是许多基础知识的基础
communication.
沟通。
So we're going to use a visual example today.
所以我们今天将使用一个可视化的例子。
That means we're going to actually look at something and talk about how to describe it well but I want
这意味着我们将真正看一些东西并讨论如何很好地描述它，但我想要
to be clear that you can use a lot of the things that we're talking about today in many other situations.
需要明确的是，您可以在许多其他情况下使用我们今天讨论的很多东西。
We're gonna start by talking about a few key words some vocabulary words and then we're going to work
我们将从讨论几个关键词开始，一些词汇，然后我们开始工作
on a few skills really important descriptions skills and then we'll do an example.
关于几个技能真的很重要的说明技能然后我们就做一个例子。
I actually have made something for you to look at and we're going to actually try to describe it together
我实际上已经为您制作了一些东西供您查看，我们将实际尝试一起描述它
that we can really get a feel for this.
我们可以真正感受到这一点。
OK.
好的。
So some basic vocabulary first before we do anything we need to know the word physical.
因此，在我们做任何事情之前，首先需要一些基本词汇，我们需要知道物理这个词。
So physical thing is something that you can touch something that you can feel something that you can
所以物理的东西是你可以触摸的东西，你可以感觉到的东西，你可以
look at.
看着。
Often we say we say an object.
我们经常说我们说一个对象。
So this word has several different meanings but one meaning of this is is a thing a physical thing is
所以这个词有几种不同的含义，但其中一个含义是事物是物理事物
often called an object.
通常称为对象。
So when we're describing a physical thing we'll use colors we'll use texture texture is the surface
因此，当我们描述物理事物时，我们将使用颜色，我们将使用纹理纹理是表面
of something but if it's not something that we're feeling then we might talk about the materials we
的东西，但如果它不是我们感觉到的东西，那么我们可能会谈论我们的材料
might talk about the materials and that means what it's made of right.
可能会谈论材料，这意味着它是由正确的材料制成的。
So there are a lot of different things that make up something that is physical.
所以有很多不同的东西构成了物质的东西。
If it's not physical then we say it is non-physical.
如果它不是物理的，那么我们说它是非物理的。
What would be something that's non-physical.
什么是非物质的东西。
Well we often called non-physical things things that happen maybe in our minds like a dream.
好吧，我们经常将在我们脑海中发生的事情称为非物质事物，就像梦一样。
Let's say you have a very very strange dream where you would describe that right but that's something
假设你有一个非常奇怪的梦，你会正确地描述它，但那是什么
that didn't really happen you can't touch it.
这并没有真正发生，你不能碰它。
And so it's non-physical or how you feel an emotion.
所以它是非物质的或你如何感受一种情绪。
Right that's a thing.
没错，就是这样。
But you can't really touch it.
但你不能真正触摸它。
So it's non-physical an idea hopes you know this sort of thing describing something that happens here
所以这是一个非物理的想法，希望你知道这种描述这里发生的事情的事情
is often non-physical.
往往是非物质的。
OK so hopes dreams ideas are non-physical.
好的，所以希望梦想的想法是非物质的。
I'm looking down to see and I'm looking down sometimes to see what I'm actually writing.
我低头看，有时我低头看看我实际上在写什么。
Just so you know OK atmosphere than atmosphere has lots of different meanings but in this case we're
只是为了让你知道 OK 气氛比气氛有很多不同的含义，但在这种情况下，我们是
using atmosphere to talk about the feeling of a place when you go into a restaurant you say oh I really
用气氛来谈论一个地方的感觉当你走进餐馆你说哦我真的
like the the atmosphere here we often also use the word vibe if you really like how a restaurant feels
喜欢这里的氛围，如果您真的喜欢餐厅的感觉，我们也经常使用 vibe 这个词
you can say this restaurant has a really really nice vibe I like the vibe here OK.
你可以说这家餐厅的氛围非常好，我喜欢这里的氛围。
This is also the atmosphere atmosphere can also be for example for a whole city.
这也是大气的气氛，也可以是整个城市的例子。
The city of Chicago has a very very cool atmosphere a cool vibe.
芝加哥市有着非常酷的氛围和酷炫的氛围。
Now you can use vibe for people.
现在你可以为人们使用氛围。
I get a very strange vibe from that guy a very strange vibe but we usually don't use atmosphere for
我从那个人那里得到了一种非常奇怪的感觉，一种非常奇怪的感觉，但我们通常不使用气氛来
people we wouldn't say you are giving me a very strange atmosphere.
我们不会说你给我一种很奇怪的气氛的人。
Probably not.
可能不是。
So we're we're going to use atmosphere in this class to talk about the general feeling of of a place
所以我们要在这堂课中用气氛来谈论一个地方的总体感觉
of a location.
的一个位置。
We also need to talk about two specific words that we're going to use later on in the class when we
我们还需要讨论两个特定的词，我们稍后会在课堂上使用它们
actually look at something.
其实看看东西。
One is cottage and a cottage is a very small simple house and it's often made of stone.
一个是小屋，小屋是一个非常小的简单的房子，它通常由石头制成。
And it's often by a lake or something near some water.
它通常在湖边或靠近水的地方。
Usually we call it a cottage.
通常我们称之为小屋。
A chimney is then something that goes on top of the house on the roof of the House and has smoke going
烟囱是在房子的屋顶上的房子顶部并且有烟的东西
through it.
通过这。
If there's a fire in the house in the fireplace in the fireplace then there will be smoke coming through
如果壁炉里的壁炉里的房子着火了，那么就会有烟进来
the chimney and usually the chimney is made of stone or brick.
烟囱，通常烟囱由石头或砖块制成。
So those two words will make sense more later in the class when we actually practice option so physical
因此，当我们实际练习选项时，这两个词在课堂上会更有意义
non-physical atmosphere the feeling of a place the vibe we need to also know cottage and we need to
非物质氛围 一个地方的感觉 我们需要的氛围 我们也知道 山寨 我们需要
know chimney we'll learn other words too later on in the class.
知道烟囱，我们稍后会在课堂上学习其他单词。
But make sure to especially remember these key words because these are important in this class.
但一定要特别记住这些关键词，因为这些在本课中很重要。